Nguyen Tien Duy

Data Engineer

+84369979413

duynguyen.data.ute@gmail.com

https://github.com/duynguyennhung

EDUCATION

Ho Chi Minh University of Technical and Education

2017 - Present

Major: Data Engineer

GPA: 2.79/4



(A) ABOUT ME

I am an open, sociable person and very serious at work. Besides that, I love working and learning new technologies. My passion is working with data, especially big data. During the college education, I also have gained a number of experience. I have been researching about your company and I would like to have an opportunity what I can work in your company.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

ASP.NET MVC Python, C, C#

Django, Tensorflow SQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL

Machine Learning Hadoop, Hive

Git, Github **ETLs**



EXPERIENCE

Data Warehouse nCovid_19

Feb 2020 - July 2020

Description: Integrate nCovid 19 data into data warehouse and data visualization.

Responsibilities: Design, develops, and implements the data architecture for a data warehouse,

including high-performance ETL tools and routines.

Uses: SSAS, SSIS, SQL Server.

Trafic sign classification

Aug 2020 – Jan 2020

Description: The website classifies traffic signs by pictures with 43 different types of signs which are possible for everyone to recognize and learn about them.

Responsibilities: Data cleaning, design model, build a simple web interface with framework Django.

Uses: Tensorflow, Django, algorithm CNN, KNN, VGG.

Data migration Feb 2020 - Fresent

Description: Compare the efficiency of different NoSQL types with PostgeSQL using TCP-H benchmark.

Responsibilities: Explore and manipulate different types of databases.

Uses: MongoDB, PostgreSql.

